<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Now on Tan Ho</title>
    <link>/tags/now/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Now on Tan Ho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/now/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - Oct 2020</title>
      <link>/now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now/</guid>
      <description>Things that have my attention Revisiting early-2020 / pre-pandemic goals now in an effort to end 2020 on par with where I started it:
 Restarting physical training and working towards regaining habits: cleared out garage space for my erg and brought home my lifting rack, barbell, and weights. Already have clocked three erg workouts last week, hoping to work my way up to five sessions per week this month between weights and ergs, and then up to an hour a day by end of year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - Nov 2019</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2019-10-29-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2019-10-29-now/</guid>
      <description>Things I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On I&amp;rsquo;m excited to be making the full-time dive into a data career - and that it&amp;rsquo;s in real estate feels like a tremendous blessing, meshing my domain knowledge with my data dev passions. Thus far, it’s been everything I’d dreamed about!
A whole season of rowing has come and nearly gone - I&amp;rsquo;ve got some regrets about not making the most of it, especially since I had the opportunity to.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - June 2019</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2019-06-09-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2019-06-09-now/</guid>
      <description>Things I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On  Incredibly excited to get back into the swing of rowing again - looking forward to both rowing and coaching. Regrouping on physical fitness - I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the past half-year undoing last year&amp;rsquo;s progress and have to eliminate the new bad habits I&amp;rsquo;ve picked up. Got lots of data/FF projects to work on, as well as fantasy football articles waiting to be written.  Need to focus on one step at a time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - May 2019</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2019-05-18-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2019-05-18-now/</guid>
      <description>Things I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On  I feel the winds of God today; today my sail I lift.
 A sudden and unexpected loss of work has me reeling right now, and I&amp;rsquo;m feeling done in property management. I need to regroup and figure out where I want to go next.
Taking a minute to count my blessings  I&amp;rsquo;m blessed to have the support of my family, and am grateful for the opportunity to travel and see them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - Mar-April 2019</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2019-03-01-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Mar 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2019-03-01-now/</guid>
      <description>Things I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On Building out DynastyFF tools/writing. Settling in at new apartment. Refocusing/re-organizing energy at work. Getting back into fitness.
DynastyFF I&amp;rsquo;ve been a bit surprised by the positive reception that my work has been getting - in February I was approached by DLF and FFStatistics for writing positions! I&amp;rsquo;m signed on with DLF and am working on some analytics projects with them as well as a few articles on league bylaws.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - Jan-Feb 2019</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2019-02-02-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Feb 2019 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2019-02-02-now/</guid>
      <description>Things That I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On Finishing up reflections on 2018 and setting out on new goals for 2019. Moving. Launching a new website!
Reflections on 2018 2018 was an important year of my life - a catastrophic collapse of my long-term relationship led to a single-minded drive to rebuild my identity. Along the way, I lost 75 pounds, rowed over a million on-water meters, helped coached a successful recreational rowing program, got a dog, and made a lot of new friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now  - Nov-Dec 2018</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2018-11-27-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2018-11-27-now/</guid>
      <description>Things That I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On I started the year with setting up a bevy of goals, some of which felt unattainable - specifically, weighing 200 lbs and rowing a 7 minute 2K test. This was pretty ambitious [delusional?] for a guy weighing ~275 pounds with a previous best of 9 minutes.
Well, I&amp;rsquo;m a heck of a lot closer than I thought after eleven months (215 lbs and 7:22), so I&amp;rsquo;ve doubled down on those goals and am determined to do my damnedest to hit those marks by Dec 31 of this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - Feb 2020</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2020-02-17-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2020-02-17-now/</guid>
      <description>Things I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On Pressing the reboot button I woke up recently and realized that I&amp;rsquo;d slumped into a funk again, which seems to be a recurring theme for me sadly. I&amp;rsquo;m pressing the reboot button on myself.
Work is going well - I&amp;rsquo;m excited about the projects, friendships I&amp;rsquo;ve made, and personal growth. I&amp;rsquo;m keen on continuing to challenge myself there.
That&amp;rsquo;s about the only thing that&amp;rsquo;s going well though.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - July 2020</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2020-07-30-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2020-07-30-now/</guid>
      <description>Things that have my attention  Wrapping up v1.0.0 of ffscrapr and submitting it to CRAN Dipping my toes into unsupervised ML via SFBX strategy analysis, PCA, and clustering Advanced R Book Club continues to be a highlight Coaching rowing (3x/week) is a nice anchor in my routine Moving, again - not exactly thrilled about this one  Ideas I&amp;rsquo;m chewing on  Hell Yeah or No - as a tool for figuring out what to do when feeling scattered/overcommitted (a lot lately!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - June 2020</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2020-06-25-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2020-06-25-now/</guid>
      <description>Things I&amp;rsquo;m Focusing On Quarantine, like it has for everyone, has been difficult. I was already struggling with work-life balance as of my Feb post, and it seems like a switch to working from home did not help on that front. I&amp;rsquo;ve succumbed to the pattern of rolling out of bed into my desk chair, banging out my hours of work, taking a nap, eating, and then back onto my only other hobby&amp;hellip;which is also R/Shiny programming but for fantasy football.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Now - Sep 2020</title>
      <link>/now-archive/2020-09-09-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/now-archive/2020-09-09-now/</guid>
      <description>Things that have my attention  Feeling at least a little burnt out. Trying to figure out what my Hell Yeah is right now. My problem is that nothing really feels hell yeah. Expressing my current mindset in MonkeyUser comics: work deadlines, 9-5 - coaching is no joy right now, and instead just another brick stretching my daily energy box. Advanced R Book Club wrapped up, which is sad/scary and yet impressive nonetheless.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>