<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rowing on Tan Ho</title>
    <link>/rowing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Rowing on Tan Ho</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/rowing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Lifting for Rec Rowers</title>
      <link>/rowing-lifting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rowing-lifting/</guid>
      <description>Lifting weights is the best way to build strength, which translates to peak power in rowing. This is a guide intended for the adult rec/masters rower looking to improve that strength (both over the offseason and as supplemental training during the rowing season.)
Philosophy Thoughts  &amp;ldquo;Better athletes are better rowers.&amp;rdquo;
 In targeting the average rec/masters rower, I&amp;rsquo;m making a few basic assumptions:
 Time is limited. We are working adults balancing busy schedules, not varsity athletes with the time to dedicate two-a-days six days per week specifically to rowing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Regatta Cheatsheet</title>
      <link>/regatta-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/regatta-guide/</guid>
      <description>The ORC Rec Guide to Regattas A guide to everything regattas: a packing list, approximate scheduling, de-rigging and re-rigging, trailer loading, rules of racing, race plans, and more.
Contents  Equipment List Scheduling De-Rigging and Rigging Trailer Loading Rules of Racing Race Plans  Equipment List A list of gear to pack in your regatta bag.
  Three wrenches: 10mm, 7/16&amp;rdquo;, and an adjustable - you will need all three!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short Mobility Warmup</title>
      <link>/rowing-warmup/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rowing-warmup/</guid>
      <description>The few short minutes before ORC Rec practices are often hectic as everyone rushes over after work, gets coach boats and equipment ready, and then hops into a boat. That said, I&amp;rsquo;m hoping to add another wrench into the works this year - a short dynamic warmup to promote mobility and get ourselves ready for rowing.
Short Description Two sets of the following circuit:
 Halos (5 reps in each direction)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coxie Cheatsheet</title>
      <link>/rowing-coxie/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/rowing-coxie/</guid>
      <description>The ORC Rec Guide to Being a Coxswain on the Ottawa River Created by: Peter Aubin with contributions from Lauren E and myself
[Download PDF Version Here]({{ site.baseurl}}/files/coxie.pdf) Congratulations, you&amp;rsquo;re in charge. Your rowers expect you to be clear, prepared, and commanding - speak up!
Responsibilities  Provide clear, loud, and commanding instructions to rowers Navigate and steer the boat  Required Items  Cox box and headset - found in upstairs office, make sure cox box turns on and headset fits into cox box Life jacket (Bay 2), whistle and lights (your own)  Delivering Instructions General Principle: Make sure your rowers understand the instruction before doing the action!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>